The Guide to the Jerome Charyn Papers 1937-1997 MSS.044
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries A: General (1955-1997)
    - Genies, Bernard, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 10 (Ga - Gn))
    - Germanacos, Nickolas C., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 10 (Ga - Gn))
    - Gibbons, R., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 10 (Ga - Gn))
    - Gieniewski, Cz., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 10 (Ga - Gn))
    - Gilman, Richard, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 10 (Ga - Gn))
    - Ginsburg-Baran, Maria, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 10 (Ga - Gn))
    - Girard, Pierre, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 10 (Ga - Gn))
    - Gleichmann, Gabi & Lee, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 10 (Ga - Gn))
    - Goethals, Thomas R., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gores, Dori J., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gofman, Patrick, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gold, Ivan, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Golden, Arthur S., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Goldleaf, Steven, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gonzalez y Fernandez-Corugedo, Santiago & Perez Lorido, Rodrigo, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Goodman, Eric, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gordon, William E., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gormley, Peggy, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gotler, Joel, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gottesman, Irene, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gould, Eric, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Green, Shirley M., Special Assistant to President Bush for Presidential Messages, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Grejnowski, Olivier (O'Grej), undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Grimaldi, Laura, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gross, Joseph M., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Grossman, Peter, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Grumiaux, Frederic, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Grunberg, Leslie F., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Guerriero, Mary, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Guttmann, Karen B., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gutwillig, Robert A., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Guyon, Jeanne (Editions Payot & Rivages), undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Gwathmey, Charles, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 11 (Go - Gz))
    - Haas, Pascale, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Haber, Leo, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Halbert's, Inc., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Hall, Charlotte (Charlotte Steinberg), undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Halper, Harriet, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Hamalian, Leo, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Hamel, Goulven, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Hamster Productions, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Handelman, Seymour N., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Hansen, Ron, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Hancourt Brace Jovanovich, Publishers, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Harris, Dermot, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Harvard University Press, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Hassan, Ihab, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Haudejin, Didier, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Haugoubart, Virginia, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Hawkes, John, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Hawley, Kristin, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 12 (Ha))
    - Hersh, B., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Hickins, Michael, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Higgins, Timothy, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - High School of Music and Art, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Hill and Wang, Inc., Publishers, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Hoffer, Klaus (Forum Stadtpark), undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Hofstra University, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Horn, Maurice, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Horovitz, Israel, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Horowitz, Glenn, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Houston, Robert, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Howell, John M. (Southern Illinois University at Carbondale), undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Huerre, Patrice, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Hugot, Gerard, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Hurwitz, Harry (Hesh), undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Hutter, Donald, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 13 (Hb- Hz))
    - Ide, Richard Alan, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 14 (I))
    - The Ingram Merrill Foundation, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 14 (I))
    - International Association of Crime Writers, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 14 (I))
    - Interno Giallo Editore, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 14 (I))
    - Iparreche, Alejandro Elias, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 14 (I))
    - Irving, John, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 14 (I))
    - Israel, Peter, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 14 (I))
    - Israel, Yonaran, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 14 (I))
    - Jakubowski, Maxim (see also: Zomba Books), undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 15 (J))
    - James Brown Associates, Inc., undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 15 (J))
    - Jarcelliz, Henry, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 15 (J))
    - Jesus, Lorraine, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 15 (J))
    - Jonathan Cape Limited, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 15 (J))
    - Joseph, Bernard, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 15 (J))
    - Joseph, Gerhard, undated; 31142040612312 (Box 1, Folder 15 (J))
    - Kahn, Helen, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kaldheim, Peter, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kaminsky, Albert, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kane, Pascal, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kaplan, Livingston, Goodwin, Berkowitz & Selvin Law Offices, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Karpman, Dahhe, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kasterine, Dmitri, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Katz, Laura, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Keane, James R., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kerber, Colette, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kessler, Charlotte, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kermoal, Francois, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kieffer, Eduardo Gudino, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Killard, Jacqueline (Secretary to J. P. Donleavy), undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kincannon, Clive, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kislak, Samuel, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Klein, Roger H., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Klein, William, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Koch, Edward I., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kocrewerski, Tadeush, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kra, Siegfried J., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Krot, Barry S., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kruger, Michael, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kubrick, Stanley, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kupcinet, Irv, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Kustow, Michael, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 16 (K))
    - Labrosse, Mrs. Jose, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - La Cantonade, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lannuzel, Marie, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lattes, Nicole (NiL Editions), undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - La Polla, Franco, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - LaSalle, Peter, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lawrence, Eve, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lawrence, Seymour, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - LeClan, Tom, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lebrun, Michel, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Leebron, Fred, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lehman, William, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Le Livre International De La Paix, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Leman, Gerard, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lesher, Andrea, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Levadoux-Feuillette, Dominique, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Levin, Beatrice, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Levine, Jill, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Levita, Phyllis, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Le Vot, Andre, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Levy, William Turner, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lewicki, Zbigniew, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lewis, Jerry D., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Liberaki, Rita, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Libraries a Marseille, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Library Journal, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lit, Walt, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Little, Brown and Company, Publishers, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Litwak, Leo E., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lloyd, David, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lolli, Maria, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lopat, Bruno, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lopez, Martina, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lorenzen, Murray V., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lotringer, Sylvere, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lousiana State University, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lowen, Alexander, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 17 (L))
    - Mailer, Norman, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Major, Clarence, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Mako, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Malin, Irving, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Mandel, Bryna, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Marcus, Janet, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Marcus, Louis, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Marquis - Who's Who, Inc., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Martens, Michel, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Martineau, Gilbert, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Matthews, Mopsy, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Matthieussent, Bruce, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Mauroc, Daniel, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - McElroy, Joe, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - McGuane, Thomas, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - McMurtry, Larry, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Meadow, Lynne, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Menegaldo, G., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Menegaldo, Helene, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Mervis, James Ian, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Meyer, Danielle, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Mewshaw, Michael, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 18 (Ma- Me))
    - Michael Joseph LTD, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Midstream: A Monthly Jewish Review, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Milazzo, Lee, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Miller, Sophie, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Ministere de la Culture, France, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Mirkowicz, Tadeush, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Mirsky, Mark, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Mizrahi, Moshe, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Mo, Hugh H., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Montemarano, Dan, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Moore, Glenn, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Morgenstern, Susie, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Mosley, Walter, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Muraire, Andre, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Mysterious Press, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Mystery Writers of America (Mary Frisque), undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 19 (Mf- Mz))
    - Nabatoff, Dawn, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - Nabokov, Vera, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - Naples, Marge, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - Natali-Perat, Nicole, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - The Nation, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - National Endowment for the Arts, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - National Foundation on the Arts and the Humanities, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - Nelson, Arnold G., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - Neiman, Nanscy, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - Nemerov, Howard, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - The New York Review of Books, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - New York Society Library, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - The New York Times, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - The New York Times Book Review, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - New York University, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - Newbaum, Teresa, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - Nicolai, C., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - Nobbe, G., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - Nyren, Neil, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 20 (N))
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 21 (O))
    - Odren, Richard, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 21 (O))
    - O'Donnel, Pat, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 21 (O))
    - O'Dwyer, Paul, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 21 (O))
    - O'Luckie, Shawn, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 21 (O))
    - Oppenheimer, Joel / Maier, Teresa, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 21 (O))
    - The Orange Public Library, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 21 (O))
    - Orsenna, Eric, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 21 (O))
    - Osheroff, Raphael, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 21 (O))
    - Ozick, Cynthia, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 21 (O))
    - Pack, Robert, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Packard, Wingate, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Pailles, Lionel, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Paine, George F., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Palczewski (Bernstein), Denise R., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Papaleo, Joe, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - The Paris Review, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Partisan Review, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Parrett, Evelyn, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Pasquier, Sylvaine, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Pastan, Linda, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Peck, David, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Peck, Gregory, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Peck, Thomas Whiting, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - PEN. A World Association of Writers, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - PEN American Center, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Penguin Books / Penguin USA, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Penn, Arthur, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Pennac, Daniel, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Petillon, Pierre-Yves, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Petropoulos, Stauros, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Petroski, Catherine, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Phillips, Robert, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Philips, Marcin, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Picilli, Evelyn, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Picon-Kalich, Molly, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Playboy, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Plummer, W. (People Weekly), undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 22 (Pa-Pn))
    - Podbielski, Anthony K., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 23 (Po-Pz))
    - Police Department, the City of New York, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 23 (Po-Pz))
    - Porco, Peter, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 23 (Po-Pz))
    - The Portable Stanford, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 23 (Po-Pz))
    - Postec, Ziva, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 23 (Po-Pz))
    - Powers, Ron, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 23 (Po-Pz))
    - Princeton University, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 23 (Po-Pz))
    - Prochazka, Juri, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 23 (Po-Pz))
    - Prudon, Herve, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 23 (Po-Pz))
    - Publishing and Communications Ventures, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 23 (Po-Pz))
    - Quarry, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 24 (Q))
    - Quest/77, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 24 (Q))
    - Rabinovitz, Robert, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Ralpho: Agence de Presse Photographique, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Rajon, Florence, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Raney, William, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Reeve, Frank, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Reichard-Megwinoff, Wanda M., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - The Review of Contemporary Fiction, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Richardson, Pippa, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Robbins, Kenn, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Roberts, Thomas N., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Rodde, Lilian, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Rodin, Frederick, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Rosen, Al, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Rosenfeld, Ruth, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Ross, Greg, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Ross, Jean W., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Rossignol, Jean, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Roth, Philip, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Rubinstein, Olivier, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Rusconi Editore, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 25 ( R))
    - Salamon, Julie, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Salon du Livre, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Saltzman, Art, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Sanchez, Serge, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Sanchez, Thomas, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Sara Films, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - San Francisco Unified School District (Minnette Ker-Higgins), undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Sarant, Vasiliki, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Sassone, Barbara, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Saxon, Edward, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Saz, James, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Schecter, Samuel, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Schmid, Thomas, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Schmidt, Chris, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Schorer, Mark, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Schneider, Jerome, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Schonfeld, Eike, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Schwarz, Joseph, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Scott, Barry, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Seed, David, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Seine Saint-Denis Conseil General, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Sekey, Susanne, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Sembler, Arlene, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Semenov, Julian, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Serpent's Tail Publishers, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Seward, William W., undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Sheekar, Amelie, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Sherer, Stan, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Shine, Stephanie, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Shonte, Peter, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 26 (Sa-Sh))
    - Sieder, Kit, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Silverman, Bennet Hugh, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Silbert, Layle, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Silbersack, John, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Simon-Ross, Selia, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Simon and Schuster, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))
    - Sinclair, Clive, undated; 31142040612320 (Box 2, Folder 27 (Si-Sz))